<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jianbo Jiao - University of Oxford</title>
    <link>https://jianbojiao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jianbo Jiao - University of Oxford</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jianbojiao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Postdoctoral Researcher in the Department of Engineering Science at the University of Oxford, and a member of the Biomedical Image Analysis (BioMedIA) group and the Visual Geometry Group (VGG), advised by Prof. Alison Noble and Prof. Andrew Zisserman. I obtained my Ph.D. in Computer Science from City University of Hong Kong, advised by Prof. Qingxiong Yang and Prof. Rynson W. H. Lau. I have been lucky to work as a visiting scholar in the Image Formation and Processing(IFP) group at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign (UIUC), advised by Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_publications/</guid>
      <description>Self-Supervised Contrastive Video-Speech Representation Learning for Ultrasound
Jianbo Jiao, Yifan Cai, Mohammad Alsharid, Lior Drukker, Aris Papageorghiou, Alison Noble
International Conference on Medical Image Computing and Computer Assisted Intervention (MICCAI), Oral Presentation, 2020
[PDF] [BibTeX] [PDF] [BibTeX] -- Unified Image and Video Saliency Modeling
Richard Droste*, Jianbo Jiao*, Alison Noble (*Equal contribution)
European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), Spotlight Presentation, 2020
[PDF] [BibTeX] [Short Video] [Long Video] [More Results] [Project] [PDF] [BibTeX] [[Project]](https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_teaching/</guid>
      <description> 2015 - 2018 (CS@CityU)  Computer Graphics (CS4182/CS5182) Multimedia Technologies and Applications (CS4185/CS5185) Computer Vision for Interactivity (CS4187) Computer Programming (CS2311) 2012 - 2015 (ECE@PKU)  Digital Media Software and System Development (04703920) Fundamentals of Digital Media Technology (04713901)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jianbojiao.github.io/post/_services/</guid>
      <description> Conference Reviewer:  AAAI 2021, WACV 2021, CVPR 2020, ECCV 2020 (Outstanding Reviewer), MICCAI 2020, AAAI 2020, IJCAI2020, ACCV 2020, ICCV 2019 (Outstanding Reviewer), CVPR 2019, MICCAI 2019, Pacific Graphics 2018 Journal Reviewer:  IEEE T-PAMI, T-IP, T-MI, T-NNLS, T-CSVT, T-Cybernetics, T-MM, Multimedia, Signal Processing Letters; Neurocomputing, Journal of Visual Communication and Image Representation (Outstanding Reviewer), Computer Vision and Image Understanding, Computer Graphics Forum </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>